Well, would you look at this!
There are so many different rooms!
Don't get too excited, now.
Besides,
love hotels aren't really
very convincing, anyway...
I wasn't comfortable leaving her at home
while away on business,
This room is so beautiful!
and I'd be fine staying
at a cheap business hotel,
and yeah, a love hotel is
a little embarrassing but...
Oh well!
This is the besssst!
It makes me so happy to
see you this pleased, Akane!
And I'm sure it has nothing
to do with us being in a place
where it's easy
to pressure me into sex!
Hey, Akane?
And there it is!
Hey, so I've got a really
long meeting this evening,
so I kinda gotta go and prep
for that in the meantime, y'know?
Understood.
Then I shall remain on standby so
that I do not interfere with your work.
Wow, guess she really can read the room.
All right, see you tomorrow, then!
Looking forward to it!
See you then!
And she seriously hasn't
done anything since then?!
I was expecting her to come and
perv out on me,
but no, nothing...
- Akane?
- Yeah?!
- Is your meeting over now?
- Yeah.
Here we go.
Now it's coming.
Well then, shall we go to sleep?
Good night!
How the heck am I supposed to sleep?!
EXCITED
She hasn't tried making a move?!
I mean, I have an early start
tomorrow, so I should sleep, but...
Calm down.
Just calm down.
- I can't take it anymore!
- Huh? The TV?!
That's really weird!
Why won't this stupid thing work?!
That woman reminds me of you, Akane.
Huh? How so?
In the way she responds during sex.
Hey, Akane?
Would you like to experience
something like that right now, too?
Oh yeah, I need it now!
You need what?
Go on, let me hear it.
You know! Don't make me say it!
- I wanna hear you beg, cutie.
- So, Akane?
What would you like me to do?
Yeah!
Please!
I need you to make me cum!
I can't say that, but...
Understood. Then leave it to me.
Nadeshiko...
Nade... shiko...
Thank you for the advice...
Mother.
I'm just glad I was
able to help, Nadeshiko!
Yes, you were a great help!
By the way,
Brought to you by ToonsHub
why did you only get in touch with me?
Call me! I miss you~~
Your Mom
Well, it's a little too early for
me to meet with your master.
I am eager to introduce
Akane to you very soon, Mother!
Hmm. Is that so?
Fine.
Once she's officially become your
master, the two of you can come visit me.
You mean it?
Then I'll try even harder to
get her to authenticate with me!